http://www.alligator.org/site/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or social media information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience;(Your information helps us better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website;(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service;(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To process transactions; orYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to more easily process future transactions if so desired.Do we use cookies?Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow, that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003 ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their profile and going to the "Subscriptions & Services" tab of that page.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not attempt to collect any information from anyone younger than 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.alligator.org/site/terms.htmlYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 12/05/2011Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.http://www.alligator.org/2700 SW 13th StGainesville, FL 32608[email protected]352-376-4458
COVID-19 Daily Numbers
This Week's Front Page
Front Page 10/05/2020
Front Page 10/05/2020
Visit our Front Page Gallery to read the full issue.
The Alligator Podcast
spotify-podcast-badge-blk-grn-330x80
Created with Sketch.
More Events
Upcoming Events
Nov
17
DigiMarCon World 2020 - Digital Marketing Conference
Tue, Nov 17, 2020
Nov
18
Commented
Articles‘Uncharted territory’: Unmasked students, fans return to pre-pandemic partying habits on game dayYoung Americans for Freedom plan on doing Gator Bait chant at football game SaturdayUF plans to hold more in-person classes in SpringUF professor fights, sues to see his fiancée againDonald Trump Jr. to host campaign event at Gainesville gun shop and shooting rangeUF Board of Trustees approve furlough policy for faculty and staffGators land high-profile transfer in Clemson running back Demarkcus BowmanVegetarian cafe fills stomachs and fulfills dreamsObedience of UF’s COVID-19 protocols varied in home openerGators pick up second win but still have much to answer for
Images
VideosSorry, there are no recent results for popular videos.
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Divisions:
Alligator:
Submit:
Classified
Letter
Submit News
Subscribe
© Copyright 2020, The Independent Florida Alligator and Campus Communications. 2700 SW 13th St Gainesville, FL - [ Terms of Use | Privacy Policy ]
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
